[
    {
        "id": "81",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 10 like Physics, 5 like Maths, and 5 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            8,
            10,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correct": 5
    },
    {
        "id": "58",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 5 like Physics, 6 like Maths, and 1 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            7,
            7,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "id": "80",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 5 like Physics, 8 like Maths, and 3 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            3,
            7
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": "72",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 1 like Physics, 10 like Maths, and 1 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            10,
            10,
            0,
            4
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "The initial value was 7, and the new value is 10. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            43.0,
            51.0,
            42.0,
            44.0
        ],
        "correct": 43.0
    },
    {
        "id": "64",
        "question": "The initial value was 7, and the new value is 5. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            -31.0,
            -29.0,
            -23.0,
            -25.0
        ],
        "correct": -29.0
    },
    {
        "id": "92",
        "question": "The initial value was 2, and the new value is 9. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            350.0,
            358.0,
            346.0,
            352.0
        ],
        "correct": 350.0
    },
    {
        "id": "89",
        "question": "An athlete's chances of qualifying for the Highland Games changed from 1% to 1%. What is the absolute percentage change and the relative percentage change?",
        "options": [
            "Absolute: 3%, Relative: 23.0%",
            "Absolute: 0%, Relative: 0.0%",
            "Absolute: -2%, Relative: -5.0%",
            "Absolute: 2%, Relative: 17.0%"
        ],
        "correct": "Absolute: 0%, Relative: 0.0%"
    },
    {
        "id": "81",
        "question": "An athlete's chances of qualifying for the Highland Games changed from 5% to 4%. What is the absolute percentage change and the relative percentage change?",
        "options": [
            "Absolute: 3%, Relative: 35.0%",
            "Absolute: -1%, Relative: 11.0%",
            "Absolute: 1%, Relative: 20.0%",
            "Absolute: 2%, Relative: 31.0%"
        ],
        "correct": "Absolute: 1%, Relative: 20.0%"
    },
    {
        "id": "100",
        "question": "The numbers are [9, 2, 6]. What is their average?",
        "options": [
            3.9,
            5.67,
            7.93,
            7.23
        ],
        "correct": 5.67
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "The numbers are [5, 8, 10]. What is their average?",
        "options": [
            10.04,
            6.63,
            7.67,
            9.29
        ],
        "correct": 7.67
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "In a group of 29 students, 1 are boys. What is the ratio of boys to the total number of students?",
        "options": [
            "4:29",
            "1:29",
            "9:38",
            "1:30"
        ],
        "correct": "1:29"
    },
    {
        "id": "90",
        "question": "In a group of 21 students, 5 are boys. What is the ratio of boys to the total number of students?",
        "options": [
            "10:21",
            "12:29",
            "5:26",
            "5:21"
        ],
        "correct": "5:21"
    }
]